

Mateusz Fonfara

Full Stack Developer

My passion is creating tools for other people to make their life easier. I have experience with each stage of creating applications, from its concept, by the design and architecture planning to final execution and deployment.

I run a blog on medium.com where I share my thoughts on the IT world and contribute to open source.

CONTACT

664 370 447

mateusz.fonfara96@gmail.com

P lława, Wyczółkowskiego 16, 14-200

matii96.github.io

SKILLS

- Vue.is
- Angular
- Node.js / Nest.js
- PHP / Symfony
- PostgreSQL / MySQL
- SoftwareArchitecture

LANGUAGES

English B2 (FCE exam)

INTERESTS

- History
- Cycling

WORK HISTORY

2018-06 - Software Architect, Full Stack Developer Current ITM Software House, Olsztyn, Warmińsko-mazurskie

- Applied established development methodologies such as microservices and event sourcing to architecture design.
- Designed unified authorization system for all web and mobile applications
- Created migration strategies to bridge development gaps between existing software architecture and future updates.

2018-02 - Back End Developer2018-06 NETTOM, Olsztyn, Warmińsko-mazurskie (internship)

- Built databases and table structures for web applications.
- Used php symfony to build projects.

EDUCATION

- 2019-02 Master of Science: Information Technology2021-03 University of Warmia And Mazury Olsztyn
 - ◆ Thesis: Soldier support system

2018-02 - Bachelor of Science: Information Technology2018-06 University of Warmia And Mazury - Olsztyn

Thesis: Chatbot - virtual guide